[♪ "Tango italiano" by Cocki Mazzetti]
- [in Italian] Ms. Callas. here!
- Maria. here!
Beautiful.
- [photographer] Maria. here!
- [woman] You're beautiful. Maria.
[photographer] One more picture.
[reporter] Do you like Positano?
♪
- [photographer] Maria!
- [photographer 2] Maria. here!
[photographer] You're beautiful
when you smile.
[photographer] Beautiful.
[photographer] Smile!
You're beautiful when you smile.
[muffled voices]
♪
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
[♪ "Tango italiano" by Cocki Mazzetti
playing on gramophone]
[in French] Oh. shit!
[upbeat music plays]
- Come on. Get out.
- Okay. okay.
Hey!
Wait here.
So... what's your name?
You want my home address too?
- No. I just wanted to...
- Be my friend.
Make me think of you as a person.
a fellow woman.
so that if it ever came to it.
I'd think twice?
No. Not at all.
[Alice sighs]
My name's Sabine.
From?
Africa. France...
Nowhere.
[man] Sabine!
Come on.
The boss wants to speak with you.
[upbeat music plays]
[woman. in French] The number
you have dialled does not exist
or cannot be reached.
Adele Caetani.
Welcome.
[suspicious music plays]
You are not Adele.
No.
[in French] You got the wrong sister.
you idiots!
[in French] Well...
She's not the hotel manager.
She's just some bratty kid.
She won't know the security codes.
the cameras. the patrols.
Do you want to call it off?
Call it off? No. Sabine. no...
We adapt.
She's the one who wanted
to screw with her father's hotel.
She must be the black sheep of the family.
This could be even better.
- Even better?
- Yes...
[in French] Wow! Great plan. guys.
[in English] She speaks French?
[lapping of the waves]
Game on.
[Daniel] Who took her. Bruno?
Who took her?
They will kill me.
Okay.
[Bruno pants]
No...
Oh. you're not that guy.
[in Italian] This is Carmela.
She's named after my ex-wife.
[Bignè] When she left me.
it was a stab in the heart.
[in English] Tapered shape.
Comfy handle.
[Tancredi] Slices and dices
like nobody's business.
Thank you. sir.
[in Italian] Nunzia...
My ex-wife number two.
[in English] Japanese. I believe.
Less knuckle clearance.
but the tip pierces concrete.
What are you doing. guys?
[Bignè. in Italian] Hilda. German.
My ex-wife number three.
[in Italian] Number three.
[in English] Sexy man. sexy life.
Guys. guys. please... Please!
Hilda truly shines
in the heavy-duty tasks.
She strips meat... to the bone.
Quick.
Clean.
[Tancredi] But Hilda...
Hilda is temperamental.
Very.
She needs frequent sharpening.
[Bignè] All the time.
- Again. again. again...
- I'll take that.
[in Italian] In these cases
normally we use a long-blade knife.
with a sharp tip. for deboning.
But today. my friend.
I chose this for you.
It's perfect
for cutting tendons and ligaments.
Daniel...
It's precise.
No!
No...
[in English] French! French!
[in Italian] They're French! French!
They are French!
[in English] They come down here
every summer!
- They rob the tourist villas. okay?
- Names.
Fuck you.
Names.
[pants]
Okay. okay. okay. okay.
The boss is Laurent.
[Bruno] Laurent...
Sabine. Bastien. Le Bris.
I don't know their second names!
Don't look at me! I don't know!
I only know they...
They're staying in a castle!
- A castle?
- Yeah. a sort of castle!
I know all the castles in the Costiera.
Which castle?
What the fuck
do you care about the castle?
It's a Medieval castle. okay?
I don't know!
They're like... squatting!
I don't know where it is!
Why take Alice?
She was angry with her father.
She said that there were
a lot of rich people in his hotel.
She said that we could rob them.
- She said or you said?
- She said.
Okay. maybe it was me.
I don't know. I don't remember!
I told you. we were... We were drunk!
She was drunk and when she woke up.
she didn't want to rob her daddy anymore.
By then it was too late.
you had already promised the Frenchies.
That's why you pulled the gun.
Fuck.
Laurent fucking hates Villa Costiera.
- Where is he?
- I don't know! I only talked to Sabine!
- I've been more than patient with you...
- But that's the truth!
- Where is Laurent?
- [Bruno] I don't know!
Where the fuck is Laurent?
- [Bignè] Oh! Oh!
- [indistinct shouting]
[Tancredi] Hey! That's enough!
[Bruno yells]
- [Bignè] Stop!
- [Tancredi] Hey!
- [yells]
- [Daniel] Get off me!
[Bignè] Daniel. stop!
Get out of here! Go. go!
[Daniel] Where is he?
- [Bignè] Wait! Wait!
- [Daniel] Get off!
[Tancredi] Easy. man.
Easy. man.
That went rather well.
[chuckles]
Fuck.
- [Genny] Good.
- Tracker.
[Bignè pants]
[Daniel] Nice work. Genny.
Do you think he'll meet 'em?
Well. he delivered Alice.
[Daniel] Bruno is not a one
that would miss a payday.
Run. rabbit. run.
[upbeat music plays]
[sighs]
You're the best.
The best.
[in Italian] Hey Fefè.
have you found my phone yet?
Not yet. Did you try the app?
It's off.
For tomorrow's auction.
I thought we were making
the dishes from that chef.
Dad doesn't want that.
Dad. have you seen my pink phone?
She called me.
My phone called you?
No. Alice. I spoke to her.
Alice?
She is coming home.
- How did you talk to her? When?
- This morning. she's fine.
- She's coming home.
- Good.
See?
Everything works out.
["Il dolce suono - Lucia di Lammermoor"
by Maria Callas playing on gramophone]
[in French] Magnificent.
Her voice...
Perfection.
Do you like opera?
No...
You're too young.
Do you play petanque?
[in English]
It's a very under-appreciated game.
I can't imagine why.
It's like chess on gravel.
So many tactical considerations.
Amazing.
[phone rings]
What do you want?
What do you think I want?
I delivered the girl. I want my money!
Money. money. money!
I want my 20. plus 2.000.
Call it commission.
Let it go.
Who is it?
Bruno.
[upbeat music plays]
Tell him we'll give him
whatever he wants.
Oh. is that the big fromage?
I'll text you where to meet.
[Bruno] No. no text.
He said. "Whatever I want."
Tell him my price just went up.
I want...
30k.
Listen...
No "listen". 30k. I want my money.
How do you say? "Au revoir". Sabine?
[in French] You deal with him.
[in English] It's alright. I'll go.
Bruno knows me. He trusts me.
So. what are you waiting for?
Come on!
Doesn't count.
Your foot was outside the circle.
- What do you mean? It was in.
- Le Bris?
Out.
Eh.
[phone beeping]
That was a wicked performance back there.
with Bruno.
I almost believed
you actually lost your shit.
But then again.
I've never seen you actually lose control.
You know. MacKenzie said
you didn't quit the Marines.
Said you got kicked out.
What did you do?
[phone rings]
- Hello?
- Did you know Alice called my father?
She said she's coming home.
Is she?
Things got a little complicated
since then.
[in Italian] Daniel. come on...
[in English] You don't have to protect me.
Alice is in trouble.
[tense music plays]
[in English] When I was a child.
my parents used to holiday in Positano.
In a cheap hotel. with no sea view.
I was bored. They were boring.
The world was black and white.
[Laurent] So. I would sneak
into other hotels for fun.
One day. at Villa Costiera.
I saw a crowd.
[Laurent] It was Maria Callas arriving.
Around her neck. a necklace
created by true masters of the form.
Are you going to tell me why I'm here?
Saturday night.
that very necklace
is to be auctioned at your hotel.
And you're going to steal it?
Maria Callas promised it to me
with a smile.
[Laurent] I tried to follow her
into Villa Costiera...
But your father got in the way.
You're not going in there.
[in French] Move!
And your grandfather
threw me out of the hotel.
Why don't you scram. you little prick?
Fuck you. old man!
Like I was dirt.
I have nothing to do with the hotel.
You are the black sheep of the family.
aren't you?
You must have sneaked into that hotel
hundreds of times.
breaking curfew.
bringing boys in or girls...
I don't judge.
The point is
you know the security blind spots.
You think I'm going to help you?
Hi.
I think a little encouragement
is called for.
[lapping of the sea]
From the auction house?
Yes. Mr. Caetani.
We'd like to run for security
for tomorrow night.
That would be
my General Manager's purview.
My firstborn... Adele.
[lively classical music plays]
Excuse me. The waiter said
you wanted to make a complaint.
May I ask you what the problem is?
I'm lonely.
I'm sorry. you're what?
Please. sit.
I'm working.
You don't get a break?
I am the manager.
No. I don't get a break.
So. you're the boss.
So. sit.
You look like you're carrying
the weight of the world.
What harm can it do to sit in the sunshine
just for a moment?
You don't take "no" for an answer. do you?
You know. actually I'm working too.
But you'll never guess
what I do for a living.
If it's what it looks like.
I'd have to kick you out of the hotel.
What do you think I do?
[whispering] Male escort?
Oh! Okay.
Mm.
I see.
Thanks. I'll take that as a compliment.
It's not.
No?
So... what do you do?
Not brain-surgery. I'm guessing.
Let's say
I'm interested in beautiful things.
[bellboy clears throat]
- [in Italian] Augusto is looking for you.
- Not now.
[bellboy] It seems urgent.
[in English] I have to go. Excuse me.
Maybe next time.
If you're lucky...
- We are very excited.
- It is exciting.
Excuse me.
Ah...
[in Italian] I've got things to do.
Can you take care
of the auction house people?
I'm going.
And would you ask Daniel
if he's heard from Alice?
Otherwise I can do it.
Of course.
[man whistles]
Who is that?
No idea.
[camera click]
- Good morning.
- The Lammermoor collection.
[upbeat music plays]
He's turning off.
You think Alice might be here?
[Daniel] Shit.
[Daniel] That's her.
That girl in the car. she's one of them.
Keep going. keep going.
Let's find a back road.
Here comes the money!
There is no money. you idiot.
- [Sabine] You got the wrong sister!
- Calm. calm. calm. calm.
Fuck.
[bees buzzing]
[ominous music plays]
This is the worst day of my life.
Can I close my eyes?
I'm going to go back now
and tell the very obsessive man I work for
that you're buried out here.
What?
Get in your car and go.
If he ever finds out that's not true.
we're both dead. Understand?
- Understand?
- Yes. understand.
- [Sabine] For once keep your mouth shut.
- Yes... On my grandmother's life.
[ominous music plays]
- Any sign of Alice?
- No.
- What happened?
- [Daniel] I'm not sure. honestly.
[Daniel] There.
[in French] Follow the girl?
[in English] Yes. ma'am.
- You're not gonna tell me. are you?
- It's not important. Drop it. please.
It's not unimportant.
And we're not chasing dog thieves.
And I don't like guns.
[sighs] Why did you get kicked out?
[melancholy music plays]
My last posting was in Yemen.
[Daniel] Gathering intel on enemy targets.
I befriended a Yemeni shepherd... Nabil.
Great guy.
Developed him as a source.
He knew all about Al Qaeda
beddown locations. its hideouts.
[Daniel] He had a beautiful family.
a wife. a young son.
[in Arabic] Thank you.
Thank you.
[Daniel. in English]
And we promised them
that we'd get 'em
out of the country safely.
But then Central Command
jumped the gun on the intelligence and...
blew his cover.
[Daniel] Rebels took the whole family.
Nobody fucking told me.
I didn't find out till I was back at base.
and I lost my shit.
I got into it with a three-star general.
and knocked him out.
- Fuck.
- Yeah.
Dishonourable discharge
and 19 years of service down the drain.
Eyes on the road. Counsellor.
We'll get her back.
Who?
Alice.
You'll get her back.
Yeah.
[ominous music plays]
[in French] You're late.
And he's not happy.
[door opens]
[in French] I'm not going to jail
for your stupid necklace.
I don't care about your obsession.
This girl. she's not a pro.
The guy Sabine saw at the beach. he is.
We need to drop it.
You know what?
You should've gone into banking.
or fashion.
- Dad.
- [in English] Show her.
- [in French] I'm begging you.
- Show her. Come on.
[Laurent] You love your sister?
[in Italian] You piece of shit.
- [in English] Just do what I ask.
- Or what?
Something bad will happen to your sister.
And her blood will be on your hands.
Yes... or no?
If this is the main access way
to the ballroom.
you'll need to install additional cameras.
Until the sale is made. the necklace
remains under our own stewardship.
Which means the secure perimeter
around the hotel will be sealed.
Locked down.
We wouldn't want your father
to get into trouble now. would we?
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Nothing.
Let me know what you need done.
I have business to attend to.
[tense music plays]
- Thank you.
- Enjoy your drink.
Thanks.
Augusto.
[Augusto] Have you heard from Alice?
- I haven't.
- She called me.
She told me she was coming home.
That was hours ago.
Since then. nothing.
Daniel?
[in Italian] Dad.
can I talk to you for a moment?
I'm talking to Daniel...
Still nothing from Alice.
- Dad. please. I need to talk to you.
- Daniel. I'll call you back.
Same old story.
Alice says one thing and does another.
She says she's coming and then disappears.
Can you let me speak. please?
She was trying to come back.
but something happened.
What?
[tense music plays]
Maybe we should call the police.
We should do a lot of things.
Tancredi?
You got any other good disguises?
[in English] Get this freak away from me.
[in French] Go away.
- [in English] You giving orders now?
- Laurent said for me to watch her.
You might be the flavour of the month.
ma chérie.
But I've been working with the patron
a long time.
And I'll be here long after you've gone.
[♪ "Alabama" by Adele Castillon
playing through earbuds]
[♪ "Alabama" by Adele Castillon playing]
♪
[♪ "Alabama" by Adele Castillon
playing on car radio]
[song stops]
- What the hell?
- You said disguise.
As what?
This was Uncle George's shirt.
Terrible quality.
- "Zippo" we called him.
- Zippo.
Trust me. Daniel. no one in their
right mind would think this was me.
Well. go on then.
What are we up against?
One on the wall.
Armed. Handgun.
Girl's here too.
She's a crack shot with a semi.
We got at least two or three inside.
Gotta assume they're all armed.
Oh. fuck. I only brought Luisella.
Does that thing still work?
One on one. yes.
- In this case... no.
- No.
Let's go fuck 'em up.
Alright. I'm the only one going inside.
If we're not going in with you.
what are we here for?
Can I...?
[loud music playing through earbuds]
[♪ "Supermodel" by Ted Griggs playing]
[song stops]
Can I please have some food?
And water maybe?
Just a cracker or something.
[Alice] Please.
[tires screech. cars crash]
[car horn]
What in God's name are you playing at?
Get out! Come on! Out!
You were on your phone.
I'm sorry.
are you saying this is my fault?
You braked suddenly!
Because there was a cat!
Do you think I should have run it over?
Mowed it down?
Splattered it across the tarmac? Hm?
Is that the kind of man you are?
Is that who I'm dealing with here?
Pookie. we're going to be late.
This man... is a brute.
[in Italian] Enough!
Get out of here!
What the hell do you want?
[in English] No stop here! Move!
Go away!
[argument continues at a distance]
[suspenseful music plays]
Thank you.
[dishware clanking]
Hey!
Alice! Alice. open the door!
[Sabine] Fuck!
[loud voices from outside]
Le Bris?
[in French] Boss.
What is this racket?
[door opens]
[Genny] Look at him.
He looks like the kind of man
who drives without insurance.
- [clicks of the tongue]
- You know what?
You two deserve each other.
- Where do you think you're going?
- Home! We're done!
Are you going to stand for that?
I'll have you know. I'm none other
than Count Villanova-Rochester!
[in Italian] Go fuck yourself!
Okay!
Hit him. darling! Hit him!
Hey! Knock it off!
[in Italian] Here's another one.
- [in English] Now what?
- What?
What?
[in French] Go get Laurent. Quickly.
[in English] Go on your knees.
- On your knees!
- Calm. Stay calm.
Calm. please.
[suspenseful music plays]
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
[in French] Sir?
Mr. Le Bris?
[in English] How do you know my name?
[tense music plays]
Daniel?
Hide.
Hey. are you okay?
How did you find me?
Are you okay?
- You already asked.
- You didn't answer.
I could do with a drink.
[sighs]
Thank you... for finding me.
Save the thank you
till I get you outta here.
You know what to do with that thing?
You point and shoot. right?
For God's sake.
I'm just gonna... take that.
Here. just step over. She's fine.
Stay close to me.
Is my dad alright?
He's holding it together.
Your sister's helping.
- She must hate me.
- You're sisters. you'll figure it out.
This is all my fault.
Oh. that's almost never true.
[in French] You know what?
I don't actually care
what you're doing here.
It was just dumb of you to come.
[suspenseful music plays]
Come on.
[yelling. shot]
[groans]
- [Tancredi] Drop it!
- [shot]
[shots]
[Laurent] Ah!
Come on.
Alright. one of these windows should work.
What's wrong?
- I can't.
- You can't what?
They will kill Adele.
You gotta start making sense. please.
They're gonna rob the hotel. The gala.
If I don't help them...
No. they're not gonna do shit.
We'll clear out of here. call the cops
and they'll be behind bars.
But they are not behind bars now.
They are here.
Alice. we gotta go.
We don't have time for this.
[Alice] I'm sorry.
Shit!
Drop it.
[gun click]
Or don't.
Bloody guns.
[sighs of relief]
Who are you?
You're the guy from Marinella's.
The guy Sabine shot.
[in French] Shut up. Just shut up.
[in English] You work for her father?
You fucking shot me.
I should have shot you in the head.
- You seem capable.
- [Daniel] Do I?
Mm-hmm.
Maybe you are the solution to my problem.
I doubt that.
What problem?
I need to switch this...
for the real one at Villa Costiera.
There's security around that necklace.
You don't stand a chance.
[in French] Exactly.
[in English] That's why
you will do it for me.
No.
Bring me that necklace.
or you'll never see her face again.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm